gameshunters.com 2019-03-30

# Privacy Policy and Cookies | GamesHunters.com

_Last updated: **February 28, 2019**_

GamesHunters (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the GamesHunters.com website (the “Service”).

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information when you use our Service.

We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

We use your Personal Information for providing and improving the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible at <https://gameshunters.com/tos/>

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it:

  * **Comments**

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

Akismets privacy policy – <https://akismet.com/privacy/>

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it.

The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: <https://automattic.com/privacy/>.

After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

  * **Media**

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

  * **Cookies**

Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive.

We use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

  * **Embedded content from other websites**

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

Youtube Privacy Policy – <https://www.youtube.com/yt/about/policies/#community-guidelines>

  * **Links To Other Sites**

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit. Some of them are listed below:

We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

  * **Automatically-Collected   Log Information (Analytics)  
**

We automatically collect certain information about you and the device with which you access the Website. For example, when you use the Website, we will log your IP address, operating system type, browser type, referring website, pages you viewed, and the dates/times when you accessed the Website. We may also collect information about actions you take when using the Website, such as links clicked.

Cloudflare Privacy Policy can be found here – <https://www.cloudflare.com/privacypolicy/>

Google Analytics Privacy can be found here – <https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en>

If you’d like to opt out of tracking by Google Analytics, visit the [Google Analytics opt-out page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

## How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

## What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. Please contact us from the [contact form](https://gameshunters.com/contact-us/) or use Data Access Request section in the bottom of this page. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

## Why we use your Personal Data

We use your Personal Data in order to:

  * collect personal information from you such as your name and email address. For example, you may voluntarily submit information to the Website by leaving a comment or using the contact us page.
  * enhance user experience;
  * To respond to your comments or inquiries;
  * To provide you with user support;
  * To track and measure advertising on the Website;
  * To protect, investigate, and deter against unauthorized or illegal activity.

## How we use your data and data security **  
**

We do our best to keep your Personal Data safe.  We use safe protocols for communication and transferring data (such as HTTPS). We use anonymizing where suitable.

From time to time, we may use anonymous data, which does not identify you alone, or when combined with data from other parties. This type of anonymous data may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. Examples of this anonymous data may include analytics or information collected from cookies.

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

## Children’s Privacy

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 16 (“Children”).

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 16. If a parent or guardian believes that the Website has personally identifiable information of a child under the age of 16 in its database, please [contact us](https://gameshunters.com/contact-us/) immediately at and we will use our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records. You can also use Data Access Request section in the bottom of this page.

## Sensitive Personal Information

At no time should you submit sensitive personal information via comments or email to the Website, including your social security number, PAN/Aadhar card number, information regarding race or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious beliefs, health information, criminal background, or trade union memberships. If you elect to submit such information to us, it will be subject to this Privacy Policy.

## Cookies and other technologies we use

The website uses cookies and/or similar technologies to analyze customer behavior, administer, track users’ movements, and to collect information about users. This is done in order to personalize and enhance your experience with us.

A cookie is a tiny text file stored on your computer. Cookies store information that is used to help make sites work. Only we can access the cookies created by our website. You can control your cookies at the browser level and with the optin/optout pop-up for EU users. Choosing to disable cookies may hinder your use of certain functions.

**We use cookies for the following purposes:**

  * **Essential cookies** – these cookies are required for you to be able to use some important features on our website, such as logging in. These cookies don’t collect any personal information.
  * **Functionality cookies** – these cookies provide functionality that makes using our service more convenient and makes providing more personalized features possible. For example, they might remember your name and e-mail in comment forms so you don’t have to re-enter this information next time when commenting.
  * **Analytics cookies** – these cookies are used to track the use and performance of our website and services
  * **Advertising cookies** – these cookies are used to deliver advertisements that are relevant to you and to your interests. Example – third party vendors, including Google, Doubleclick and others. In addition, they are used to limit the number of times you see an advertisement. They are usually placed to the website by advertising networks with the website operator’s permission. These cookies remember that you have visited a website and this information is shared with other organizations such as advertisers. Often targeting or advertising cookies will be linked to site functionality provided by the other organization.

**Google AdSense & DoubleClick Cookie – **Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our website.

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website or other websites.
  * Google’s use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of personalized advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](http://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2&lang=EN).

[**For our site’s pages, there is a an opt-in and opt-out consent pop-up for EU users.**](https://gameshunters.com/gdpr/)

### Manage cookies on your browser

You also can remove cookies stored in your computer via your browser settings. Alternatively, you can control some 3rd party cookies by using a privacy enhancement platform such as [optout.aboutads.info](http://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2&lang=EN#!%2F) or [youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/). For more information about cookies, visit [allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

For the management of cookies and your choices, the configuration of each browser is different. It is described in the help menu of your browser, which will allow you to know how to change your selection for cookies:

  * **Google Chrome**

[https://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=en&hlrm=en&answer=95647](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en&hlrm=en)

  * **Microsoft Internet Explorer**

<https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies>

  * **Microsoft Edge**

<https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-10-microsoft-edge-and-privacy>

  * **Apple Safari**

<https://support.apple.com/guide/safari/manage-cookies-and-website-data-sfri11471/mac>

  * **Mozilla Firefox**

<https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences>

  * **Opera**

<https://help.opera.com/en/latest/web-preferences/>

### Cookies Found in GamesHunters

## Changes To This Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to make change to this Privacy Policy.

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

_Last updated: **February 28, 2019**_

## Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please [contact us](https://gameshunters.com/contact-us/).

## GDPR Data Access/Removal Request

If you want to access/remove your personal data or unsubscribe from this website(eg comments, contact forms), you can request it below(or contact us).
